ukclimbing.com 2007-08-14

# UKC - Privacy Policy

UKClimbing.com Ltd has created this privacy statement as a demonstration of our firm commitment to the privacy of visitors.

The following contains information regarding privacy issues on the UKClimbing.com Website as they relate to information gathering, posting, or third party participation.

* * *

**Message Boards:**  
Message Boards are one of the interactive public areas of the UK Climbing Website. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these message boards becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information.

**User Profiles:**  
UKClimbing.com Ltd allows its users to set up a personal profile which can be viewed by other UKC users.

  * User Profiles are not compulsory to use the site but un-registered user are restricted from some sections of the site.
  * The information is collected via the input box when and is submitted by the user. Information is stored on a non public database on our server.
  * Email addresses are not publicly disclosed on the site.

The mailing list is held on our web server (computer), which is based in the UK.

UKClimbing.com Ltd does not divulge your registration information to any third parties.

**Links**  
Every once in awhile, UKClimbing.com Ltd may post a link to another Websites (i.e. news article). UKClimbing.com Ltd is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites.

**Banner Ads**  
This site, UKClimbing.com, uses its own Banner Ad system. No information is collected via Cookies.

**Cookies**  
UKClimbing.com Ltd uses cookies in its price list to remember the contents of your shopping basket and your address details for return visits.

**Disclosures**  
We will not pass your information to any third parties if you have told us not to.

**Website Statistics**  
Visitor IP addresses are logged as part of the daily Website statistic gathering. This is a common occurrence on the majority of Websites. It is used only for the accurate reporting of statistic information.

UKClimbing.com Ltd is dedicated to your privacy and we hope that this privacy statement is a testament of our privacy commitment.

If you have any questions, concerns, or requests regarding the UKClimbing.com Ltd Privacy Statement, please feel free to contact the UKClimbing.com Ltd by mail or email:

Andy Hyslop, UKClimbing.com Ltd, Unit 6 Shoreline Business Park, Sandside, Milnthorpe, Cumbria, LA7 7BF. UK Tel: 0870 753 7748
